// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q008: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: '------ you find any mistakes in the brochure, please contact the museum office as soon as possible.',
      choices: ['Should', 'Because', 'So that', 'In case of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Should'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Three letters of ------ are required to apply for the position of accounting manager at Drexel Pharmaceutical.',
      choices: ['referred', 'refer', 'referring', 'reference'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['reference'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ who have registered for a subscription to the magazine will receive the latest issue of the magazine within a week.',
      choices: ['Anyone', 'Whoever', 'Each', 'Those'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Those'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The development team for the EX01 model has found it ------ to complete that model by September.',
      choices: ['difficultly', 'difficulty', 'difficulties', 'difficult'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['difficult'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Sandeep Technologies is ------ to recycling programs as one of its environmental initiatives.',
      choices: ['dedication', 'dedicated', 'dedicating', 'dedicatedly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['dedicated'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'It is advisable to prepare answers to ------ possible questions at the upcoming workshop.',
      choices: ['every', 'all', 'another', 'much'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['all'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The City of Orange Bay was able to successfully complete a musical event featuring local artists ------ a lack of funding.',
      choices: ['although', 'nevertheless', 'unless', 'despite'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['despite'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Climbing & Gearâ€™s camping tents are lighter and more durable than ------ of its competitors.',
      choices: ['them', 'that', 'these', 'those'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['those'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'By implementing the marketing strategy ------ by Mr. Adams, the theme park has seen a significant increase in the number of visitors.',
      choices: ['devising', 'devised', 'devise', 'devises'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['devised'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Whitfield ------ several errors in the inventory control manual and reported them to her supervisor.',
      choices: ['persuaded', 'detected', 'reminded', 'replaced'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['detected'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}